banqer.co 2017-04-20

# Privacy | Banqer

We want everyone to enjoy using Banqer. For these reasons we've like to reassure you of what will will and won't do with any information you provide or create in Banqer. Please read our privacy policy below make sure you're in the know. 

Any capitalised terms used in this policy have the meanings given to them in Banqer’s Terms of Use. 

### Privacy:

The Service is an online financial literacy tool provided by Banqer. In order to provide the Service, Banqer may collect some personal information about you. 

### Privacy Protected

Where you provide personal information to us, we will comply with the Privacy Act 1993 (New Zealand) and other applicable privacy laws (“Privacy Laws”). 

### Collection and use of Personal Information:

The personal information provided by you to us is collected, and may be used, for: 

  1. providing or improving the Service,
  2. monitoring website usage and compliance with this Agreement;
  3. carrying out internal research and development; 
  4. providing information to you about additional products or services that may be of interest to you; or
  5. If you are a Teacher or an Institution on a Sponsored Plan, providing billing details (names and email addresses) of users accessing the Service under that plan to Banqer’s sponsorship partner, for auditing purposes only.

### Collecting and use of aggregate User Data and User Submissions:

You agree that we may retain and aggregate User Data and User Submissions, including your User Data and User Submissions, for marketing purposes and may provide aggregate User Data and User Submissions to third parties, provided that such use does not enable the identification of any individual, i.e. is anonymised. If you are acting on behalf as an agency for the purposes of the Privacy Laws, you agree to ensure that you collect, use, hold and process any User Data and User Submission in accordance with your obligations under the Privacy Laws. 

### International storage of User Data and User Submissions:

You agree that we may store User Data and User Submissions (including any personal information) in secure servers overseas, for example the United States, and may access User Data and User Submissions (including personal information) in countries such as the United States and New Zealand, from time to time. 

### Security breach:

If you become aware or suspect that any unauthorised person has obtained, or attempted to obtain, access to User Data or User Submissions or has used or attempted to use User Data or User Submissions for purposes not authorised or permitted by this Agreement:

  1. you must immediately notify us; and
  2. we may at our discretion take such steps as are reasonably available to us to identify that unauthorised person and to prevent that access. To avoid doubt, where the unauthorised access or use is by a Private User or a student, teacher or employee of an Institution, or is caused by a breach of this Agreement by a Private User or a student, teacher or employee of an Institution, the relevant unauthorised or breaching person must pay us reasonable costs related to taking such steps.

### Disclosure:

In addition to any circumstances allowing us to use or disclose personal information under the Privacy Laws, we may use or disclose your personal information where reasonably necessary to investigate any complaint or to protect your, our or another person’s rights or safety. 

### Sale of business:

If we enter into an agreement for a bona fide sale of our business (assets or shares, whether in whole or in part) to a third party, your personal information may be transferred to the third party purchaser. You acknowledge and agree that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Banqer or its assets may continue to access and use the User Data and User Submissions as set out in this Agreement. 

### Cookies:

We may store personal information through the use of cookies. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that the Website transfers to your computer’s hard drive to enable our systems to recognise your browser. 

For visitors to our Website that have not created an account with us, we may use cookies to track the user as they navigate the Website and to improve the Website’s usability. These cookies do not collect any personal information about the user.

If you set up an account with us, we may use cookies to manage the signup process, to remember who you are while you are using the Service, to track your use of the Service and to improve the Service’s usability. These cookies will usually be deleted when you log out of the Service, however in some cases they may remain after you have logged out to enhance the experience when you return to the Service at a later date. 

From time to time we may test new features and make subtle changes to the way the Service is presented. When we are testing new features, cookies may be used to ensure that you receive a consistent experience while using the Service, whilst also ensuring we understand which changes our users appreciate the most. 

We also use cookies provided by Google Analytics to track things such as how long you spend on the Service and the pages that you visit. For more information on Google Analytics cookies, see the official Google Analytics page. 

You can prevent the use of cookies by adjusting the settings on your browser (see your browser help for how to do this). Be aware that disabling cookies will affect, or may disable some or all of the functionality and features of the Service. 

### Personal information:

To the extent that we collect, hold or process any personal information contained in your User Data and User Submissions in the course of providing the Service to you, you acknowledge that we act as your agent for the purposes of the Privacy Laws. You must obtain all necessary consents to enable us to collect, use, hold and process that information in accordance with this privacy policy and our terms of use. 

### Access to personal information:

You have the right to access and request correction of any personal information that we hold about you. Please contact [privacy@banqer.co](mailto:privacy@banqer.co.nz) if you would like to request any personal information or wish to raise any complaints or concerns. 

### Law:

This Privacy Policy and its interpretation and operation are governed by the laws stated below, and you and we agree to be subject to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the country set out below . You agree not to raise any jurisdictional issue if we need to enforce a judgment in that country. 

If you are domiciled in: | the governing law is the law of: | and we and you submit to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of:  
---|---|---  
Australia  |  Australia  |  Australia   
United Kingdom  |  England  |  England   
New Zealand or any other country not listed above  |  New Zealand  |  New Zealand
